MIKE: I got the Strangler.
我发现那个杀人犯！
Wabash and Van Buren.
在华比和范拜仁！
Oh, shit.
啊，混蛋！
Oh, shit!
MIKE: Jack, get the van.
杰克，去范那边
Eddie, help me!
艾迪，救我！
Eddie, Eddie, don't leave me! God, no!
艾迪，别丢下我！天啊，不！
Give it up, Ray. It's over.
投降吧，雷！结束了！
片名：《鬼娃回魂》
Oh, God, I'm dying.
天，我要死了
(SHOUTING) You hear this, you son of a bitch?
听到了没，你这个杂种？
I'm gonna get you for it!
我会那样对你！
I'm gonna get you,
我会抓住你
and I'm gonna get Eddie,
我会抓住艾迪
no matter what!
无论如何！
I gotta find somebody.
我要找个人
I don't know. I gotta find somebody.
我不知道，但我要找个人
Gotta find somebody.
我要找个人
CHARLES: Give me the power, I beg of you!
给我力量吧，求你！
BOY 1 ON TV: I have no friends. No one will play with me.
我没有朋友，没有人会和我一起玩
BOY 2 ON TV: Uh-oh.
啊噢，
There's a friend in need.
我需要一个朋友
Hey, cheer up.
嘿，振作点
Who are you?
你是谁？
I'm a Good Guy.
我是一个公仔
I've just come from the Good Guy Clubhouse,
我刚刚从公仔俱乐部来
and I'll be your friend to the end.
我永远都会是你的朋友
You will? You mean you'll be my friend now?
会吗？你意思是你现在也已是我朋友了？
Sure, I will.
当然是了
Hidey-ho.
嗨
I saw this one.
我看到这个了
MAN ON TV: All right, good guys,
好了，公仔们，
that's our Good Guys show for today,
这就是我们今天的公仔秀
but don't go away,
但别离开
because we've got a very important Good Guy message just for you.
因为我们有很重要的公仔信息给大家
MASCOT ON TV: Hi, Good Guys. Boy, have I got news for you.
嗨，公仔们，孩子，我有一些新闻
Now you can have your very own Good Guy doll.
现在你可以拥有自己的公仔了
That's right.
是的，
You can have all the adventures we have on TV in your very own home.
你可以在自家的电视里体验所有的冒险经历
Good Guys say three different sentences.
公仔们，说三句不同的话
We even turn our heads and blink our eyes when you talk to us.
在你跟我们说话时，我们甚至会闭上眼睛和转过头
Right, Oscar?
对吧，奥斯卡？
Hi, I'm Oscar, and I'm your friend to the end. Hidey-ho.
嗨，我是奥斯卡，我会是你永远的朋友，嗨！
Wow!
哇！
MASCOT: Every Good Guy has a name all his own,
每个公仔都有他自己的名字
so he can be your very own best friend.
这样他才能成为你最好的朋友
So remember to tell Mom and Dad you want a Good Guy.
所以要记得跟你爸妈说你要一个公仔
Perfect for birthdays or just any old time.
最好在你生日或任何节日的时候
And remember, you can buy all of our Good Guy accessories, too.
记住，你还可以买任何公仔附件
- Right, Oscar?
- Right.
- 是吧，奥斯卡？
- 是的
MAN ON TV: Brought to you exclusively by Play Pals,
如此独一无二的经历由“好玩伴”带来，
makers of Good Guys and other fine toys.
他是公仔还有其它好玩具的制作人
Found in toy stores throughout the greater Chicago area.
在芝加哥范围内的玩具店来买吧
Mommy, wake up.
妈咪，起床！
Mommy.
妈咪
Mommy, wake up.
妈咪，起床！
- Wake up, Mommy. Wake up.
- Andy.
- 起床，妈咪！起床！
- 安迪
What time is it, Andy?
几点了，安迪？
Wake up.
起床
6:30. It's only 6:30 in the morning.
6:30，现在才是早上6:30
But it's a beautiful day outside. See?
但今天外面天气很好，看到了没？
lt certainly is.
当然了，
How long you been up, birthday boy?
你起来多久了，小寿星？
Since forever.
很久了
I made you breakfast in bed.
我在床上就已帮你弄好早餐了
You did? Oh, God.
你做的？噢，天啊
Well, thanks.
好棒，谢谢
Well, this looks just excellent.
啊，它看起来很美味
Oh, I'll tell you what.
噢，我会告诉你那是什么的
Why don't I eat this just a little later, okay?
我迟一点再吃这些东西，好吗？
Mmm-hmm.
嗯
But first, I gotta give you your super-duper ，birthday tummy-gummy.
首先，我先给你一个超级生日礼物
Come here. Come here. Come here.
过来这边，过来这边，过来这边
- That's one. How many years old are you today?
- Two.
- 就是它，你今年多大了？
- 两岁
Happy birthday, pumpkin.
生日快乐，小不点
Thanks. Can we open my presents now, Mommy?
谢谢，我现在可以打开我的礼物吗，妈妈？
Yes, we can.
是的，可以
Terrific!
好极了！
FEMALE ANNOUNCER ON TV: Good morning, Chicago. Leading off at this hour,
早上好，芝加哥，现在开始播报
Charles Lee Ray, the notorious Lake Shore Strangler was shot and killed
查尔斯·李·雷，声名狼籍的杀人犯
shortly before 3:00 a.m. this morning on Wabash Avenue.
今天早上3点前在华比街被枪杀
Can I open this first, Mommy? Can I, can I?
我可以先打开他吗，妈咪？我可以吗，我可以吗？
Andy, don't you want to start with the smaller one first?
安迪，你为什么不先看那个小一点的呢？
Okay, go ahead.
好的，继续
Well, what do you think? You need these clothes so badly.
好吧，觉得怎么样？你很需要这些衣服
Hey, I think they're gonna be okay.
我想它们还好啦，
We'll just have to take them up just a couple of inches.
我们只需剪去几英寸
What's the matter?
怎么啦？
Nothing.
没什么
Oh, I know. You want some toys, don't you?
我知道了，你想要一些玩具，是吧？
Not boring old clothes.
而不是讨人厌的破旧衣服
Try the other one.
试试这个吧
Well, what do you think?
怎么样？
I want a Good Guy to go with it.
我想要一个配套的公仔
I know you do, Andy.
我了解，安迪，
But I didn't know about it in time this month to save up for it.
但这个月因为事先不知道就没来得及凑钱
- Karen.
- Hi.
- 凯伦
- 嗨
You know that doll that you wanted for Andy?
你知道你想买给安迪的那个公仔吧？
- The one that costs 100 bucks?
- Yeah, the Good Guy doll.
- 100块的那个？
- 是的，公仔
There is a peddler in the alley behind the store,
这商店后面有一个小贩，
and I think he's got one.
我想他可能有那玩意
What? What would a peddler be doing with a doll?
什么？为什么小贩会有？
Who cares? Would you grab your purse and come on? We can get a deal on it.
管那么多干什么？你买不买？我觉得很划算
But I can't just leave my counter.
但我不能离开柜台啊
Do you want the damn doll or don't you?
你到底想不想要啊？
- Of course I do.
- Well, then, come on.
- 当然要
- 那快点
- Come on.
- All right.
- 慢点
- 好了
There he is.
他在那里
Okay, show her.
好了，给她看看
Well, is it a Good Guy or not?
这是公仔吧？
lt is. lt is.
是的，是的
Yeah, well, I told you.
是吧，我没骗你
How much do you want for it?
多少钱？
50 bucks.
五十块
- 10 and not a penny more.
- 30.
- 最多10块
- 30块
What, are you kidding? That thing is not worth $30.
什么，你开玩笑吧？那玩意不值30块
Enough. Take it or leave it. Somebody else will buy it.
行了，不买走人，会有人买的
- I'll take it.
- Karen, it's too much money.
- 我买
- 凯伦，这太贵了
No, it isn't. You have no idea how much Andy wants this doll.
不，不贵，你不知道安迪有多想要这个公仔
But we don't even know if the damn thing works.
但我们不知道它是不是好的
Here you go, lady. May it bring you and your kid a lot of joy.
给你，女士，希望它能给你和你的孩子带来快乐
KAREN: Thank you.
谢谢
Hey, hold on, you!
嘿，你等等！
How do we know the damn thing isn't stolen?
我们怎么知道这鬼东西是不是偷的？
Steal this.
偷这个
MAGGIE: Steal this yourself.
肯定是你偷的
(LAUGHING) Maggie.
玛吉
I think I dated him.
我想我是不是跟他约会过
Come on. We gotta get back to work.
快点，我们要回去工作了
Andy's gonna love it!
安迪肯定会喜欢的！
Mrs. Barclay, so nice of you to drop by. Have a nice break?
巴克利夫人，你顺道过来真好，玩得很开心吧？
I'm sorry, Mr. Criswell. I was only gone for a minute.
对不起，克利斯威尔先生，我们只离开了一会儿
Have a heart, Criswell.
通融一点吧，克利斯威尔
We were just downstairs buying her little boy a birthday present.
我们只是到楼下帮她儿子买一件生日礼物
We have specified break times for activities like that, Miss Peterson.
我们可以在休息时间干这事，彼得森小姐
Mrs. Howe has taken sick, and we're shorthanded tonight.
毫尔太太病了，我们又缺人手
You'll have to fill in for her.
你代替一下吧
I can't. I have to pick up my son at the day care center in an hour.
不行，1小时内我得去日托中心接我儿子
I'm sorry, this is an emergency.
对不起，这是紧急情况，
Wait a second. I'll take over for her.
等等，我来代替她吧
Miss Peterson, you work in shoes, not in jewelry.
彼得森小姐，你在鞋柜那边干活，而不是珠宝柜
You'll just simply have to do it.
你必须做，
Now, you can take off at 5:00,
你可以在5点离去，
but you'll have to be back at 7:00.
但7点时要赶回来
It's my son's birthday.
今天我儿子生日
Mrs. Barclay, are you happy with your job here?
巴克利夫人，你对这份工作还满意吧？
Yes, of course I am.
是的，我很满意
- Then I suggest that...
- Hey.
- 那么我建议你...
- 嘿
Chill out, would you, Walter?
很扫兴，不是吗，华特？
I'll take care of Andy for you.
我替你照顾安迪
Maggie, you can't do it again.
玛吉，你不能再这样做了
Don't be silly. It'll be the hottest date I've had in months.
别傻了，这会是几个月来最重要的约定
I can't imagine why.
我无法想像为啥
Hey, where are you going?
嘿，你去哪里？
Good Guys are on TV.
公仔们要在电视上出现了
Well, I may have something better for you.
我有一些更好的东西给你
What?
什么？
This isn't groceries.
这可不是普通的哦
A Good Guy! I knew it!
是公仔！我知道！
I knew you'd get me one.
我知道你买了！
Show me how he works, okay?
演示下它是怎么玩的
Hi, I'm Andy. What's your name?
嗨，我是安迪，你呢？
Hi, I'm Chucky, and I'm your friend to the end. Hidey-ho.
嗨，我是恰奇，我会是你永远的朋友，嗨
Wow! He's something, isn't he?
哇！它真有趣，不是吗？
Oh, Mom, thanks.
妈妈，谢谢你
You're welcome, honey.
不用，宝贝
See, that's how you build things.
看，你就是这样办事的
MALE ANNOUNCER ON TV: Good evening. WDOL with a late breaking report.
晚上好，WDOL的最新插播报道
Eddie Caputo, repeated accomplice of Charles Lee Ray,
艾迪·卡普托，查尔斯·李·雷的帮凶
has just escaped the Michigan Avenue precinct.
刚刚从米其干大街附近逃脱了
More details to follow on the news at 9:00 next.
详细情况将在9点下次播报
Hey, Chucky, you're not watching me.
嗨，恰奇，你没看我
Hey, wanna play?
嗨，想玩吗？
Hey, it's time for bed, Andy.
嘿，该上床了，安迪
MAN ON TV: No, sir. Never saw the little swab before.
不，先生，我以前从没见过这个小无赖
Come on, Chucky. We have to get ready to go to bed.
来吧，恰奇，我们该准备睡觉了
BOY ON TV: I'm not a stowaway. Mr. Ghoo brought me here.
我没有逃票，古先生带我来的
MAN: And who might Mr. Apple be?
苹果先生是哪位？
Aunt Maggie, Chucky wants to watch the 9:00 news.
玛吉阿姨，恰奇想看9点的新闻
Sure he does.
他当然想
Okay, kid, off we go.
好了，孩子，走吧
Come on. There we go.
快来，走吧
Chucky.
恰奇
Oh, yes, Chucky.
噢，对，恰奇
You, too. Off we go.
还有你，走咯
Now, it's brush your teeth and under the covers with you.
现在去刷牙然后睡觉
Okay? Agreed?
行吗？同意吧？
Good. Okay.
好极了
You yell when you're ready for me to tuck you in.
你准备好了，就大叫一声，我才可以开始
Hey, Chucky, want to see my room?
嗨，恰奇，想看看我的房间吗？
Andy, are you brushing your teeth?
安迪，你在刷牙吗？
Yes, Aunt Maggie.
是的，玛吉阿姨！
Good.
好
ANNOUNCER ON TV: And now, Action News at 9:00.
现在是9点新闻
TERRY: ln Washington today,
今天在华盛顿，
the mayor replied
市长回复
that he would study the congressional findings carefully
他会仔细研究国会所裁决的
and have the commission on gang-related violence issue recommendations to him.
还会考虑一些团体犯罪问题
Back to you, Steve.
交回给你，史提夫
STEVE: Thank you, Terry.
谢谢，特里
In other news, police have now clarified the information
警方已澄清了一些事实
regarding the escape of Eddie Caputo.
关于艾迪·卡普托的逃脱
Authorities say that Caputo managed to elude his captors
官方宣称他躲过了警方的追捕
while being transferred onto a prison bus on his way to court. Of course...
在他从监狱被送去法院的途中
Okay, mister, what do you have to say about this?
好，先生，关于这个你想说些什么？
About what?
说什么？
Come on. Come on.
来啊，来啊
You know, you have to learn that when I say something, I mean it.
你知道吗？当我要你做啥的时候你必须听话
But what did I do?
但我干了什么？
You know what I'm talking about.
你知道我在说什么的
Turning the TV on and putting Chucky in front of it
你打开电视并把恰奇放到它前面
when I told you it was time to go to bed.
在我说你该上床睡觉的时候
I didn't do that.
不是我做的
Oh, no? What did Chucky do?
不是？那是恰奇干的咯？
Walk into the living room and turn it on all by himself?
走到起居室，自己打开电视？
Did you do that, Chucky?
是你干的吗，恰奇？
Andy, stop it. Now, come on, under the covers. Hurry.
安迪，够了！现在盖上被子！快点
But, Auntie...
但是阿姨...
Under the covers and not another word.
盖上被子，别再说话了
But I didn't put Chucky in front of the TV.
但我并没有把恰奇放到电视机前
Enough. Okay?
够了，行吧？
Give me a kiss.
亲我一下
Good night, baby, and happy birthday.
晚安，宝贝，生日快乐
Good night, Aunt Maggie.
晚安，玛吉阿姨
I told you she'd be mad at you if you watched the news.
我说过如果你看新闻的话，她会抓狂的
MAN ON TV: I missed you, my dear.
我想你，亲爱的
I was afraid you weren't going to show up.
恐怕你得去参加表演了
Too bad about the accident.
事故太严重了
WOMAN ON TV: Yes. Papa told us they just found it.
是啊，爸爸告诉我们他们找到了
How did you know?
你怎么知道的？
MAN: I must have heard it somewhere.
我一定是从什么地方听来的
WOMAN: I haven't seen you in so long, darling.
我好久没见你了，亲爱的
I mean, couldn't we take a little walk, or something?
我是说，我们能不能一起走走，或者干点别的
lt looks as though you haven't had a breath of fresh air in days.
看起来你很久没有呼吸过新鲜空气了
MAN: A walk?
WOMAN: Of course.
- 散步？
- 当然了
The air outside will do you good.
外面的空气对你有好处
Besides, you'll work up an appetite.
另外还可以促进你的食欲
Please.
去吧
MAN: But, Janice, surely it's going to rain.
但是，珍尼丝，要下雨了
Andy?
安迪？
MAN: Depends on whether there's an indictment.
根据有无起诉事宜
WOMAN: Well, they don't always...
好吧，他们并不总是...
Andy, is that you?
安迪，是你吗？
How did that happen?
那是怎么回事？
Uh... Hello?
呃...喂？
Hi. How's it going? How's Andy?
嗨，没事吧？安迪怎样？
MAGGIE: Karen?
凯伦？
Yeah. Who else would it be? ls something wrong?
是啊，还会有谁？没事吧？
Uh...
呃...
No.
没事
Everything's fine.
一切都很好
Are you sure? You don't sound like everything's fine.
你听起来不像没事的样子
No, I just had a bit of the alone-at-night willies. You know?
我只是晚上一个人有一点点焦虑不安，你明白吧
Now, would you stop worrying
现在，你就别担心了，
and give Criswell a kick in the pants for me?
还有你能否帮我踹克里斯韦尔一脚
You got it.
没问题
Hey, listen, Maggie. Thank you for everything.
听着，玛吉，真是很感谢你，
You're a real pal.
你真是我的挚友
Oh, yeah?
噢，是吗？
Yeah, yeah. Give Andy a kiss for me, will you?
当然，帮我吻一下安迪，
See you soon. Bye.
待会见，拜
What is wrong with me?
我究竟怎么了？
I'm scaring myself half to death.
我都快给自己吓死了
POLICEMAN 1: Step away from this barricade.
移走那路障
Come on, move it back. There's nothing to see.
挪到后面去，没什么好看的
POLICEMAN 2: Now, let's move this police line back here.
把警戒线移后点,
Go on home, folks, please.
回家吧，大家
DETECTIVE: She was on the sixth floor.
她在六楼
Miss, what do you think you're doing?
啊，小姐！你在干什么？
I live here.
我住在这里
Andy?
安迪？
Oh, no. Andy?
噢，不，安迪？
Andy?
安迪？
Andy!
安迪！
Mommy!
妈咪！
Oh, thank God.
啊，感谢上帝
Are you all right?
你没事吧？
Oh, I'm so glad. I got so scared when I...
我太高兴了，刚才太可怕了当我...
What's wrong? Where's Maggie?
怎么了？玛吉呢？
She had an accident.
她出了点了意外
Accident? What kind of an accident?
意外？什么意外？
Mrs. Barclay, I'm Detective Mike Norris, Homicide.
巴克利太太，我是迈克·诺里斯探员，调查谋杀案的
Could I talk to you out in the hall?
我能和你去外面谈谈吗？
Why? What's happened to Maggie?
为什么？玛吉出什么事了？
Please?
请告诉我？
I'll be right back.
我很快回来
Look, Mrs. Barclay...
请看，巴克利太太
What?
什么？
Miss Peterson's dead, Mrs. Barclay.
彼得森小姐死了，巴克利太太
What?
什么？
How?
怎么死的？
She fell from your kitchen window.
她从厨房的窗口摔下去了
Oh, no.
啊，不！
You all right?
你没事吧？
Yes. All right.
是的，我没事
Come on.
过来
Oh, Maggie.
噢，玛吉
Did you check over here?
你检查那边了吗？
Oh, Maggie.
噢，玛吉
You got any idea what these are?
你知道这是些什么吗？
No.
不知道
MIKE: They look like footprints, don't they? Very small footprints.
它们好像是一些脚印，是吧？很小的脚印
What are you implying?
你想暗示什么？
I don't know.
我不知道
What would Andy be doing up on the counter, right?
安迪跑到柜子上会干些啥呢？
- What?
- Besides,
- 什么？
- 另外，
I already checked his closet. None of his shoes matched these prints.
我已查过他的柜子，他的鞋对不上这些脚印
Mommy? Mommy?
妈咪？妈咪？
Chucky wanted to know what was going on.
恰奇想知道情况怎么样了
Andy, I want you to go to bed.
安迪，我要你去睡觉，
The detective and I are very busy.
我和警探现在很忙
But, Mom...
但是妈妈...
Right now, please.
现在，快去
MIKE: Andy.
安迪
What do you got on your feet?
你脚上是什么？
Good Guy PJ sneakers.
公仔运动鞋
Wow. Come here.
哇，过来这里
Can I see the bottoms of them?
我能看看它的底部吗？
Sure.
当然可以
Look at this. There's a gun. Is that a cowboy hat?
看这，那是把枪。那是牛仔帽吗？
Andy, get into bed. I'll be in in a minute to tuck you in.
安迪，快上床，我马上替你盖被子
- But, Mom...
- Right now.
- 但是，妈妈...
- 快去
Why are you treating Andy like this?
你为何这么对安迪？
If he says he doesn't know how those footprints got there, then he doesn't.
他说了不知道那里为何有脚印，他就是不知道
Look, Mrs. Barclay, somebody made those footprints.
巴克利太太，确实有人留下脚印，
If not Andy, then who?
不是安迪会是谁？
I don't know, and I don't care.
我不知道，而且我也不在乎
All I know is that I've just lost my best friend tonight to a horrible accident
我只知道我的好朋友刚刚发生意外惨死
and I would like some time alone with my son,
我要跟儿子独处一会儿，
who I'm sure is just as upset about this as I am.
他和我一样伤心
Okay. Sorry. I'm sorry.
我很抱歉，对不起
I'll clear everybody out of here right away. Okay?
我马上叫我的同事离开
Hey, guys, you done? Let's go. Chop-chop.
兄弟们，好了吗？走吧
Let's go, everybody. Out of here.
各位，我们要走了！
POLICEMAN 1: Let's clear this up over here. Come on.
收队了，走吧
POLICEMAN 2: Okay.
好了
POLICEMAN 3: Let's go, Sid.
我们走，锡德
What do you think was so important about my sneakers, Chucky?
你知道我的鞋为什么这么重要吗，恰奇？
You don't know either, do you?
你也不清楚，是吧？
Well, let me know if you find out anything about those footprints.
如果你发现了那些脚印的任何情况，请告诉我
Mommy, Mommy.
妈咪，妈咪
Mommy, I know who was on the kitchen counter. I know, I know.
妈咪，我知道当时谁在厨房柜台那，我知道，我知道
- Andy, I thought I...
- Who, Andy? Who?
- 安迪，我觉得我...
- 谁，安迪？是谁？
Chucky!
恰奇！
Your doll?
你的公仔？
KAREN: Andy, that's enough stories for tonight.
今晚的故事到此结束，
Now, come on, back to bed. Now I mean it.
现在回去睡觉，听到没？
But, Mom...
但是，妈妈...
Good night, Detective.
晚安，侦探
- What?
- Are you gonna call me?
- 又怎么了？
- 你在叫我吗？
You don't give up, do you?
你没放弃，是吧？
I just...I hate loose ends.
我只是...我不喜欢草草收场
And I hate people who don't know when to stop.
我也讨厌那些不屈不挠的人
Ouch.
哎哟！
A spirited lady.
神勇的女士
No kidding.
别开玩笑
I want that autopsy report on my desk
我明天就要
- first thing tomorrow.
- Yeah.
- 验尸报告
- 好的
And anything you can find out about Mrs. Barclay and her son.
还有你能找到的任何关于巴克利太太的信息
You got it. Anything else I can do for you, sir?
没问题！还有事吗，长官？
Oh, yeah. Here. Get this to the lab.
噢，还有这个，这个拿到实验室去
I found it in the corner of the kitchen.
我在厨房角落找到它的
What is this?
这是什么？
Possible murder weapon.
可能是凶器
No.
不是吧
Come on. You're kidding me.
得了，别开玩笑了
Hey, you are kidding me, aren't you?
嘿，你在开玩笑，是吧？
ANDY: 'Cause she saw you walking and talking?
因为她看见你能走路和说话？
I guess there was no hiding from her.
我猜她无处可藏
Andy, who are you talking to?
安迪，你在跟谁说话？
Chucky.
恰奇
Chucky, huh?
恰奇，啊？
Yeah, sure, Chucky.
是的，恰奇
He's sitting right over there.
它就坐在那里
Chucky's been talking to you, too, hasn't he?
恰奇还跟你说话，是吧？
What's he been saying?
他说什么？
All kinds of things.
什么都说
His real name is Charles Lee Ray,
他的真名叫查尔斯·李·雷
and he's been sent down from heaven by Daddy to play with me.
天堂里的爸爸命令它下凡来和我一起玩
He has, has he? Anything else?
是吗？还有其它事吗？
Yes. He said Aunt Maggie was a real bitch
是的，他说玛吉阿姨是婊子
and got what she deserved.
她会遭到报应的
Andy, how can you say something so horrible?
安迪，你怎么可以说这些可怕的事情？
I didn't say it. Chucky did.
不是我说的，是恰奇
Andy, stop it.
安迪，够了
You know perfectly well that you're making this up.
你心里清楚这是你编的！
But I'm not. Chucky's alive. Really, he is.
不，我没有，恰奇是活的，真的，他是活的
Andy, Chucky... Chucky's a doll.
安迪，恰奇？恰奇是个公仔
He's made of plastic and stuffing.
他只是一些塑料和填充剂做的
Look at him. Look at him.
瞧瞧它，瞧瞧它，
Now, does he look like anything else to you?
他像是其它东西吗？
Don't, you'll hurt him.
别，你会伤到他的
Andy, look!
安迪，看！
Now you don't really think that Chucky is alive, do you?
你不是真的以为恰奇是活着的吧，是吗？
But he is.
但他确实是
Andy, stop it. Please.
安迪，别说了！够了！
It's 'cause of Aunt Maggie you're yelling at me, isn't it?
因为玛吉阿姨死了，你才这样的，是吧？
Yes. Yes, I guess it is.
是的，我猜是的
I'm sorry.
对不起
I'll stop making up stories.
我不会再编故事了
Thanks, champ.
谢谢
Do you wanna sleep in with me tonight?
你今晚想和我一起睡吗？
No, it's all right.
不，我没事
I've got Chucky.
我有恰奇
Come on, into bed.
来，上床
Good night, sweetheart.
晚安，宝贝
I love you.
我爱你
Good night.
拜拜
You're right, Chucky. She didn't believe me.
你说得对，恰奇，她不相信我
Hi. I like to be hugged.
嗨，我喜欢被抱着
Good. I'd love to hug you, too.
好极了，我也喜欢
Hey.
嘿
You sure you're all right about last night?
你确信昨晚没事吧？
No bad dreams about Aunt Maggie?
有没有发关于玛吉阿姨的恶梦？
And Chucky's only a doll, right?
恰奇只是个公仔，对吧？
All right, off to school with you, then. I love you tons.
好了，快去学校，我爱你
MAN ON PA: 43rd street. Next stop, 47th.
43号街，下一站47号街
Is that Eddie's?
那不是艾迪的吗？
Look, you stay here. I have to go tinkle.
你呆在这里，我去尿尿
I'll be right there, Chucky.
我会在这里的，恰奇！
Chucky?
恰奇？
Mrs. Barclay.
巴克利太太？
Detective Norris, I came as soon as I got your message.
诺里斯探员，我刚收到你的消息就过来了
You haven't been to the school to pick up your son yet?
你没去学校接你儿子吧？
No. No, I came directly from work. Why?
没有，我直接从工作的地方过来的，怎么了？
Let's go into my office.
进我办公室说吧
Is something wrong with Andy?
安迪出什么事了？
Please.
请
I...
我...
I don't know how to tell you this, Mrs. Barclay.
我不知道怎么说才好，巴克利太太
Tell me what?
告诉我什么？
Do you have any idea why your Aunt Maggie fell out of that window?
你知道你的玛吉阿姨为什么会从窗户那摔下去的吗？
Yes.
知道
Could you tell me why?
能告诉我为什么吗？
'Cause she saw Chucky, and it scared her so much, she fell out.
因为她看到了恰奇，被吓坏了，然后就掉下去了
Oh, she did, huh?
是吗，啊？
(DOOR OPENING) So why did Chucky go to see Eddie Caputo?
为什么恰奇要去见艾迪·卡普托呢？
Mommy!
妈咪！
Oh, Andy.
噢，安迪
All right, sweetheart. Come on.
没事，宝贝，来
Now listen to me, okay?
听我说，好吗？
Nobody believes you about Chucky.
没人会相信你是恰奇干的
Unless you start telling the truth right now,
除非你现在就说真话
They're going to take you away from me.
他们想把你从我身边弄走
You hear that, Chucky?
听到了没，恰奇？
They're taking me away unless you say something.
说话吧，不然他们要把你弄走了
Please, say something.
求你了，说话吧
Come on, Chucky. Say something.
快，恰奇！说啊！
Tell me why you lied to me about everything.
告诉我为什么你一切都骗我
Come on, Chucky. Say something.
快，恰奇，说话呀！
Tell me.
告诉我！
Hi, I'm Chucky, and I'm your friend to the end. Hidey-ho.
嗨！我是恰奇，我会是你永远的好朋友，嗨
Mommy, he's doing it on purpose.
妈咪，他是故意的！
He told me never to tell about him or he'd kill me.
他说过我不能泄露他的秘密，否则他会杀了我
Mrs. Barclay, my name is Dr. Ardmore. I'm from County General.
巴克利太太，我是阿得莫，来自县城
I've seen more than enough.
我见的够多了
Maybe Andy should spend a couple of days with us.
也许安迪应该跟我们一起待几天
Well, say something, you little bastard.
说话啊，你个小混蛋
Say something, damn it!
说啊，该死！
Hi. I like to be hugged.
嗨！我喜欢被人拥抱
"He wants you for a best friend."
他想要你成为他最好的朋友
Yeah, sure.
当然
Hi, I'm Chucky. Wanna play?
嗨，我是恰奇！想和我一起玩吗？
Talk to me.
跟我说
Come on, talk.
快，讲啊！
I said, talk to me, damn it. All right.
我说跟我说话，该死！好吧！
Then I'm gonna make you talk!
我会让你出声的！
I said talk to me, damn it, or else I am gonna throw you in the fire!
说啊，否则我把你扔到火里！
You stupid bitch! You filthy slut!
你这蠢婊子！你这荡妇！
I'll teach you to fuck with me!
我会教你和我做爱！
No! No!
不！不！
Stop!
住手！
No.
不
No!
不！
Oh, Detective Norris!
噢，诺里斯探员！
Mrs. Barclay, what are you doing back here?
巴克利太太，你在这里干什么？
Andy was telling the truth.
安迪说的是真话
Chucky is alive and he killed Eddie Caputo.
恰奇是活物，他杀死了艾迪·卡普托
- What?
- I took him home to my apartment.
- 什么？
- 我把他带回公寓了
I was about to throw away the box that he came in when the batteries fell out.
我想把装他的盒子扔掉，突然电池从里面掉出来了
Don't you see?
你们还没发现吗？
He's been moving and talking for days without any batteries in him.
他不用电池就可以活动还有说话
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
How I found out the doll was alive.
我在说我是如何发现这公仔是活的
See, I threatened to throw him into the fireplace,
我威胁把他扔到火堆里
when all of a sudden, he came alive in my hand.
突然他就活过来了
I dropped him, and he got up and ran out of the apartment.
我扔下他，而他则跑出了房子
Good night, Mrs. Barclay.
晚安，巴克利太太
Wait a minute. I am telling you the truth.
等一下！我在告诉你事实！
He killed Maggie. He killed Eddie Caputo.
他杀了玛吉，他杀了艾迪·卡普托
Look, Mrs. Barclay.
听着，巴克利太太
I sympathize with you. I really do.
我很同情你，我真的很同情
I hated what happened in there today.
我讨厌今天所发生的事情，
But lying is not gonna help your son.
但是撒谎对你儿子没好处
Lying? Does this look like I'm lying?
说谎？我像是在说谎吗？
How did you get those?
你怎么被咬的？
Chucky bit me.
恰奇咬的
Oh, for God's sake.
啊，天啊！
All right, don't believe me.
好的，你不信！
Where you going?
你现在去哪里？
To find Chucky.
去找恰奇！
How you gonna do that?
你怎么找？
I bought him from a peddler where I work. I'll start there.
我先去找把恰奇卖给我的那个小贩
That isn't a good part of town to be in at this time of night.
那里晚上治安很差！
Mrs. Barclay, do you hear me?
巴克利太太，你听到了没？
You don't want to go down there at this time of night.
在晚上这个时候你不会要去那吧
God damn it.
该死！
Uh-huh.
呃
What's she doing here?
她在那干嘛？
Hey, excuse me.
嘿，打扰一下
Mister.
先生！
I'm not gonna hurt you. Do you remember me?
我不想伤害你的，还记得我吗？
No, no.
不，不记得
I'm sorry. I bought a doll from you
不好意思，我昨天向你买了一只公仔
in back of Carson's department store with my friend yesterday.
和我朋友一起在卡尔森商店后面，
- Doll?
- Yes, a Good Guy doll.
- 公仔？
- 是的，公仔
You sold it to me. Do you remember?
你卖给我的，还记得吗？
Oh, yeah, a doll. What about it?
噢，公仔，怎么了？
Where did you get it?
你从哪里搞到的？
What will you give me if I tell you?
我告诉你的话你会给我什么好处？
I don't have much, but you're welcome to whatever I have.
我钱不多，有的都给你
It's not enough. What else you got?
还不够，你还有什么？
That's all I've got.
就这些了
All you got?
就这些？
What are you... Yes.
你到底...是的
That's not all you got.
这不是你所有身家
- Wait a minute.
- No, you got a lot.
- 等等
- 不，你还有很多
No. No, no.
没有，没有，没有
(SCREAMING) No. Wait. No, no!
不，等一下！不！不！
Pig!
猪！
Christ, he's a cop!
天哪，他是警察！
All right. What about the rest of you?
好吧，你们几个也想试试？
You wanna party, too?
你们也想来聚一聚吗？
All right. Now, you want to answer the lady's question now?
现在可以告诉这位女士了吧？
Where did you get the doll from?
你从哪里搞到那公仔的？
I don't know nothing about no doll.
我什么都不知道
You're not gonna know nothing about nothing in a minute,
你什么都不知道啊
unless you talk to me. Now talk!
快告诉我，说！
A burned-out toy store on Wabash. That's where I got it.
华比区一个被烧毁了的玩具店，我在那里得到的
Get out of here.
滚！
What's wrong?
怎么了？
Nothing.
没事
Well, wait a minute. Something the peddler said upset you. What was it?
等等，那小贩说了些什么让你这么沮丧？
I just told you, nothing.
我说过了，没什么
God damn it. My son's life is at stake. Now, what was it?
见鬼了！我儿子很危险！究竟是什么？
The place where he said he got the doll, Charles Lee Ray died there.
他说他拿到公仔的地方，查尔斯·李·雷就是死在那里的
Who?
谁？
The Lake Shore Strangler. The man who's partners with Eddie Caputo.
那杀人犯和艾迪·卡普托是搭档
Hey. Where are you going now?
嘿，你要去哪里？
Wabash and Van Buren.
华比和范拜仁
There's nothing there. It's an abandoned wreck of a store.
那里什么都没有，那家店已经毁了，
Why don't you believe me?
为什么你不相信我？
It was struck by lightning the night that Charles Lee Ray died.
查尔斯·李·雷死时，那里被闪电击中了
How do you know that?
你怎么知道？
Because I was there. I was the man who killed him.
因为我在那！是我杀死他的！
Why didn't you tell me?
你为什么不告诉我？
It's not exactly the kind of thing you tell someone.
你不会把这种事告诉别人的
Come on, let me take you home. You need some sleep.
来吧，我送你回家，你需要休息
Did he say anything? Anything at all?
他说了什么吗？随便什么
- Who?
- Charles Lee Ray.
- 谁？
- 查尔斯·李·雷
Yeah. He threatened to kill me and Eddie Caputo.
有啊，他威胁要杀了我和艾迪·卡普托
I'm sorry you couldn't find anything to help Andy.
我很抱歉你没能找到什么可以救安迪的
I really am.
真的很抱歉
But I did.
但我知道
I found out that Chucky is Charles Lee Ray.
我发现恰奇就是查尔斯·李·雷
The only thing I don't know is how he got inside the doll.
我唯一不知道的是他怎样进入那公仔里面去的
Good night, Mrs. Barclay.
晚安，巴克利夫人
Where did Charles Lee Ray live?
查尔斯·李·雷住哪？
Look, please, will you just get out of the car?
好了，你能不能下车？
Hey, just tell me where he lived.
告诉我他住在哪里
Don't you understand? Andy's life depends on it.
你还不明白吗？安迪的性命跟这个关系很大
730 Stoney Island, the south side.
斯托岛730号，南部
But I've already checked the place out.
我查过了
There's nothing there. Now, good night.
那里什么也没有，晚安
Wait a minute. Where are you going?
等等，你要去哪里？
- Home, to get some sleep.
- No, you can't do that.
- 回家，休息一会
- 你不能那样！
Don't you see? You just said it.
你还不明白？你刚刚说过了
Chucky killed Caputo. That leaves you.
恰奇杀了卡普托，你很吃惊吗？
That does it.
是的
Oh, please listen to me.
听我说
Out.
出去
I am telling you the truth.
我在告诉你事实！
Why won't you believe me?
为什么你不相信我？
Because I'm sane, Mrs. Barclay. Sane and rational.
因为我很理智，巴克利夫人，理智而且清醒
All right. All right.
好吧！好吧！
Do you remember what you said
你还记得你遇到我的
the first night you met me in my apartment?
第一个晚上说过的话吗？
- What about it?
- You said you didn't like loose ends.
- 什么？
- 你不喜欢悲惨的结局
Well, I'm a loose end.
我已经很惨了
You can't just let go what I said tonight without checking it out.
在查清楚这件事前你别想让我走
For the last time, Mrs. Barclay, good night.
最后一次，巴克利夫人，晚安
(SINGING)
♪ Don't you lift the top
♪ When you want to see inside
♪ You can only see one thing
♪ At a time and that won't... ♪
Good night, asshole.
晚安，混蛋
Oh, god!
啊，天！
MAN: Jeez, look out!
小心！
Hi, Mikey.
嗨，麦琪
Won't do you any good, Mikey. You can't hurt me.
你这样做没用，麦琪！你伤不了我！
(SCREAMS) Karen.
凯伦
What are you doing here?
你在那里干什么？
After I talked to you last night,
在我昨晚跟你说过话后
I decided to go back to the station and pull Ray's file.
我决定回到局里并翻阅了雷的档案
I learned a couple of things.
我知道了一些事
His nickname was Chucky,
雷的小名就叫恰奇
and he spent a lot of time with this man.
他跟这个男人混了很久
Now, all we have to do is find him before Chucky does.
我们能做的就是在恰奇之前先找到他
CHUCKY: Hello, John.
你好，约翰
Over here.
这里！
Hi.
嗨
It's me. Chucky.
是我，恰奇
What do you think? The grigri work?
你怎么认为？符咒的作用吗？
You know, when I came here learning all that stuff about how to beat death,
你知道吗？我之前来学习驱鬼的时候
I thought maybe you were pulling my chain.
你可能觉得我还是个小屁孩
But not now. Not now.
但现在不是了，现在不一样
Only one problem.
只有一个问题
What?
什么？
This. I didn't think anybody could hurt me.
就是我不认为有人能伤到我
But last night, I got shot.
但昨晚我被枪击了
You know something? It hurt.
知道吗？受伤了
It hurt like a son of a bitch. It even bled.
他妈的受伤了，甚至流血了
Now why's that, John?
为什么这样，约翰？
You're turning human.
你正在转变为人类吧？
What?
什么？
The more time you spend in that body,
你寄居在身体上的时间越长
the more human you'll become.
你就越来越向人类转变
You mean I have to live out the rest of my life in this body?
你意思是我以后都得生存在这身体里？
No fucking way. You got me into this, you get me out.
没门！你把我弄到里面去，就得把我弄出来！
I can't do that, Chucky.
我做不到，恰奇
Why not?
为什么？
Because you're an abomination,
因为你很讨厌！
an outrage against nature.
你的暴行违背了天理！
You perverted everything I've taught you and used it for evil.
你扭曲了我教你做的全部事情把它用于邪恶！
And you have to be stopped.
你必须被阻止！
You know, I thought something like this might happen.
你知道吗？我早就想到类似这样的事情可能会发生
That's why I prepared for it.
所以我已经准备好了
What are you talking about?
你在说些什么？
Your own personal mojo, doc.
你自己的魔人
Give me that.
给我
Sure. How do you want it? Broken leg?
当然，你想要什么样的？断了腿的？
Shouldn't tell your customers where you hide things like this, John.
你就不应该告诉你的顾客这种东西藏在哪里，约翰
Gets you in trouble every time.
每次都让你陷入麻烦
Now how do I get out of this body?
我怎样才能离开这身子？
No, I won't tell you.
不，我不会告诉你
Yeah?
是吗？
Tell me or die, John. Your choice.
告诉我或者去死，约翰，你选择
No, I'll tell you.
不要，我会告诉你的
You have to transfer your soul out of the doll
你必须把你的灵魂传出那个公仔
into that of the first human being you revealed your true self to.
给第一个看到你真面目的人体内
You mean the first person I let in on the fact that I was really alive?
你是说只要传给第一个知道我是活的人就行了？
I don't believe it. I just don't believe it.
我不相信，真不敢相信
The first person I let in on my little secret was a six-year-old kid.
第一个知道我秘密的是一个6岁的孩子
I'm gonna be six years old again.
我又要变成一个6岁的小孩
Well, John, it's been fun, but I gotta go.
约翰，真有趣，但我会干
I have a date with a six-year-old boy.
我和那小孩还有约
And you have a date with death.
而你则和死神有约
So long, John.
再见，约翰
Hold it. Wait, wait.
别急！等等！等等！
Oh, my God.
啊，老天
- Too late.
- What?
- 太迟了
- 什么？
Must save the boy. Must...
一定要救那小孩，一定...
Must get his soul
必须把他的灵魂
into him like he got into doll.
放进他的身体就像他进入公仔的身体里一样
What?
什么？
You must stop him before he can say the chant.
你必须在他唱出圣歌前阻止他
Kill him before he can say it.
在他说出来前杀了他
But how? How?
但要怎样做？怎么做？
The heart. His heart is almost human.
心脏，他的心几乎是人类的
It's the only way. Through the heart.
这是唯一的方法，穿过心脏
Help me! Help me! Dr. Ardmore, Chucky's here!
救我！救我！阿得莫医生，恰奇在这里！
Help me! He's coming to kill me! He's here. Chucky's here.
救命！他要来杀我！在这里！恰奇在这里！
I don't see anybody.
我没看到有人
But, Doctor, Chucky's here,
但是医生，恰奇在这里
and he's going to kill me.
他要杀我
But Chucky is here, and he's going to kill me!
恰奇在这里，他要杀我！
He's going to kill me.
他要杀我
Please don't leave me. Please.
别丢下我，求你了
No!
不！
ARDMORE: Andy, stop.
安迪，别动！
ATTENDANT: Hey, wait a minute.
嘿，等等
Stop him!
阻止他！
MAN: Check the north corridor.
查一下北面的走廊！
Easy. Easy, it's all right, Andy. It's all right.
放松，放松，没事的，安迪，没事
You're not gonna need this anymore, all right?
你再也不需要它了，是吗？
But I do. Chucky's in the room, and he's trying to kill me.
但我要！恰奇在房里，他想要杀了我！
No, Andy. It's gonna be all right. I'm here now.
不，安迪，没事的，我在这儿
And I'm gonna protect you.
我会保护你
Andy. Easy, boy. Easy.
安迪，放松，放松点
Come on, nobody's here.
这里没人
No, please. He'll kill you, too.
不，别这样！他也会杀了你
Andy, now...
安迪，现在...
No, please. Listen to me. Please.
不，请听我说，求你了！
Andy, now this is just gonna sting you for one second.
这只会让你疼一会
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
不要！不要！不要！不要！
Stop.
不要
What happened?
发生了什么事？
Look, miss, could you just excuse us for a minute here, all right?
小姐，你能离开一会吗？
What?
什么？
- What?
- Yeah, yeah.
- 什么？
- 是啊，是啊
Fried him to a crisp with the electric shock machine and then he escaped.
把他放到那机器里面炸成薯片，但他跑了
Escaped? Where?
跑了？哪里？
We don't know, but I bet she does.
我们也不知道，但我想她知道
Chucky. You seen Chucky anywhere?
是恰奇，你见过恰奇吗？
- Who's Chucky?
- Kid's doll.
- 谁是恰奇？
- 一个公仔
The same one that was at the station house.
跟局里那个是一样的
Have you seen him anywhere?
你见过他吗？
What am I gonna know about a doll? Where are you going?
我怎么会知道一个公仔？你们去哪？
They think Andy did it.
他们认为是安迪干的
I know, the girl said that Chucky was here,
我知道，那女孩说恰奇在这里
and that he was looking for Andy.
找安迪
- But where would Andy go?
- He'd go home.
- 安迪能去哪呢？
- 家
I always told him to go there if he was in trouble.
我说去那里如果他有麻烦的话
- Does he have a key?
- It's under the mat.
- 他有钥匙吗？
- 在门毯下
Come on. Come on. We don't have much time.
快点，快点，我们没有时间了
Look, George.
看，乔治
Some child left their doll in the elevator.
一些小孩把他们的公仔扔在了电梯里
Leave it alone.
别管它
Whoever left it there will come back looking for it.
那些扔了公仔的小孩会回来找
Ugly doll.
真丑的公仔
CHUCKY: Fuck you.
靠
(SHOUTS) Surprise!
吃惊吧！
Batter up!
打啊！
Give me the power, I beg of you.
给我力量吧，求你了
KAREN: Andy!
安迪！
MIKE: Andy!
KAREN: Andy!
- 安迪！
MIKE: Andy, can you hear me?
安迪，你能听到吗？
KAREN: Andy!
安迪！
Andy!
Stop! Ow!
站住！噢！
KAREN: Andy.
安迪
MIKE: Karen, Karen, are you all right?
凯伦，凯伦，你没事吧？
Oh, Mike.
喔，迈克
Just take care of Andy.
照顾好安迪
Karen, Karen.
凯伦，凯伦
Take this. Take it.
拿着这个，拿着
Mike!
迈克
Mommy.
妈咪
CHUCKY: What's wrong? Gun jammed?
怎么了？卡壳？
Andy!
安迪
Andy, help me. The matches.
安迪，救我！火柴！
Andy!
安迪！
Please! Now!
求你！现在！
Andy, no, please.
安迪，不要
We're friends to the end. Remember?
我们是永远的好朋友，记得吗？
This is the end, friend.
已经结束了，朋友
Oh, my baby.
啊，宝贝
MIKE: Karen? Andy?
凯伦？安迪？
You all right?
你们没事吧？
Andy, go get me the first-aid kit
安迪，帮我拿点急救包
under the kitchen sink really fast. Okay?
在厨房水槽下面
What happened?
怎么了？
Oh, God. Chucky's dead.
天啊。恰奇已经死了
Mommy, Chucky's gone.
妈咪，恰奇跑了
KAREN: Andy, hurry up.
安迪，快点
Andy.
安迪
Hello, Andy.
嗨，安迪
Mommy.
妈咪
Mommy!
妈咪！
Give me the boy, and I'll let you live.
把那男孩给我，我不杀你
Do you hear me? Give me the boy.
听到了没，把他给我
Mommy!
妈咪！
CHUCKY: Give me the boy.
把小孩交给我！
JOHN: What the hell's going on here?
这里究竟发生了什么事？
Oh, hey, hey, hey.
噢，嘿，嘿，嘿
MIKE: Karen.
凯伦
God！
天！
Oh, Jesus.
上帝！
JOHN: Yeah, I got a cop down here. Multiple stab wounds.
有警员倒下了，多处刀伤
The Brewster Apartments on North Grand Street. Make it fast.
北格兰街的部鲁斯特区，快点
All right, they're gonna be here in 10 minutes. Now, tell me what happened.
他们10分钟内到，发生什么事了？
The kid was right. The doll's alive.
那小孩说对了，公仔是活的
He almost got the three of us.
他几乎把我们3人都困住了
Come on, what are you talking about?
正经点，你胡说什么啊？
You don't believe me? All right, well, go on. Check it out in the hall.
你不信？继续到大厅里检查下
It's scattered all over the place.
他可能在这厅里的任何地方
But don't touch it. Do you understand me?
但别碰它，懂吗？
Don't you touch one part of it!
别碰它任何地方！
All right, look. Take it easy, okay?
好的，放松点
Just relax yourself, all right? All right.
放松点，好吗？
Okay, Mike. I'd like you to take a look at this thing, okay?
迈克，我想你去看看这玩意
Because there's no way this thing's alive.
因为那东西不可能还是活的
I thought I told you not to touch it.
我告诉你别碰
Mike, will you be sensible?
迈克，理智点
Come on, look. It's as dead as they come. It's dead.
看，就像死了一样，它死了
CHUCKY: Choke him! Kill him!
杀了他！杀了他！
I'll rip his throat out.
我要拧断他的脖子
Kill him!
杀了他！
Kill him.
杀了他
Kill him now! Strangle him! Don't let go!
杀了他！扼死他！别让他跑了！
JOHN: God.
天
Kill them! Kill them! Kill them all!
杀了他们！杀了他们！杀光他们！
The heart. Shoot him in the heart.
心脏！射他的心脏！
Hi, I'm Chucky.
嗨，我是恰奇
Wanna play?
想玩
You believe me now?
你现在相信我了吧？
Yeah.
嗯
But who's gonna believe me?
但还有谁信我？
Come on.
过来
All right. Ready? Here we go.
没事吧？好了没？走吧
Come on.
过来
Andy.
安迪
Come on. We're gonna go to the hospital with Mike.
走，我们和迈克一起去医院
Let's go.
走吧